Here, we set up our TensorFlow variables.
这一步 我们开始设置 TensorFlow 变量
x is a placeholder that will store our input batches.
x 是占位变量 将用来存储一批输入数据
We initialize the batch size to None,
我们将批量初始化为 None
which allows the placeholder to later accept a batch of any size,
在后面的过程中 这个占位变量就可以接受任何批量大小的输入数据
and we set the image dimensions to 32 by 32 by 1. y stores our labels.
我们将图像尺寸设置为 32×32×1 标签存储在变量 y 中
In this case, our labels come through with sparse variables,
在这个例子中 标签是稀疏变量
which just means that they're integers.
它们包含的都是整数
They aren't one-hot encoded yet.
也就是尚未进行独热编码 (one-hot encoding)
We use the tf.one_hot function to one-hot encode the labels.
我们使用 tf.one_hot 函数对标签进行独热编码处理
Now we set up our training pipeline.
现在 我们来设置训练流程
First, we have another hyperparameter to tune.
首先 还有一个超参数需要调整
The learning rate tells TensorFlow how quickly to update the network's weights.
学习速率决定了 TensorFlow 更新神经网络中权重的速度
0.001 is a good default value
0.001 是个不错的默认值
but you can experiment with other rates and see how they do.
但你也可以尝试一下其他学习速率 看看效果如何
Next, we pass the input data to the LeNet function to calculate our logits.
接下来 我们把数据输入 LeNet 计算对数几率
We used the tf.nn.softmax_cross_entropy_with_logits
我们调用了 tf.nn.softmax_cross_entropy_with_logits 这个函数
function to compare those logits to
将对数几率结果和真实标签进行比较
the ground truth labels and calculate the cross entropy.
并计算交叉熵
Cross entropy is just a measure of how different
交叉熵用于测量对数几率的分类结果和
the logits are from the ground truth training labels.
真实标签之间的差距
The tf.reduce_mean function averages the cross entropy from all of the training images.
tf.reduce_mean 函数求出所有训练图像的交叉熵平均值
AdamOptimizer uses the Adam algorithm to minimize
AdamOptimizer 使用 Adam 算法来最小化损失函数
the loss function similarly to what stochastic gradient descent does.
这和随机梯度下降算法类似
The Adam algorithm is a little more sophisticated than stochastic gradient descent,
Adam 算法优化了随机梯度下降算法
so it's a good default choice for an optimizer.
因此它也是优化算法的一个合适的默认选项
This is where we use the learning rate hyperparameter that we set earlier.
这里的超参数是我们之前设置过的学习速率
Finally, we run the minimize function on the optimizer which
最后 我们在优化器上运行最小化函数
uses backpropagation to update the network and minimize our training loss.
通过反向传播更新神经网络 以最小化训练期间的损失函数值
So this is our training pipeline.
这就是我们的训练流程
But so far, it's only a pipeline,
但目前为止 它只是一个流程框架而已
we have to actually pass data into the pipeline for it to work.
我们需要输入数据 才能使其发挥作用
We'll get to that in a few code cells.
我们将在接下来的几个代码格中介绍这部分内容